

Andzej Krupoves

Personal info

Date of birth: 1990.05.16 (32 y.)

City: Vilnius

Phone: +37060720567

E-mail: andzejkrupoves@gmail.com

My professional life started with earning a bachelor's degree in Electronics, which led me to my first job for an authorisation company as an IT engineer and later on as an Application Administrator. Afterwards, my new adventure began in Australia, where I had to learn new skills such as dealing with customers face to face as a manager for a non-profit organisation. Throughout my journey in life, I study most of the time technical stuff which potentially might lead me to new experiences from a customer service/NOC (dealing with IT tech), testing coding (as QA) and consequently I would consider a junior programmer position and a final stop would be a Technical Project Manager.

Work experience

2022.08 - 2023.04

Company: Revel Systems

Company website: revelsystems.com

Position: Tier 1

- End-user consulting via phone, and e-mail.
- Finding common ground between a user and me to set up a particular feature for Pont Of Sale (POS)
- Troubleshooting network, primarily LAN
- Tracking concerns and tasks through Salesforce as a formal media for informal slack
- Guiding an end-user on how to set up different card readers (EFT) and troubleshoot them
- Guiding end-user with Apple products mostly iPads.
- Adopt different terms on the go since clients can call from the US, Australia or Canada or Europe.

2022.03 - 2022.05

Company: CUJO AI

Company website: cujo.com/ Position: Junior NOC Analyst

- -Monitoring, using such tools as Grafana, Kibana, Chronograf, Opsgenie etc.;
- -Direct communication either with the external parties or internal through Slack, Teams, and emails;
- -Registration, escalation, allocation tickets, incidents via JIRA, and other related to

business nuances such as creating Confluence pages, etc.

2019.06 - 2019.11

Company: Oz Tech

Company website: www.oztechcopier.com.au

Position: IT technician

Laptops/Desktops hardware repairing; Preparing servers, computers for customers; Communication with clients, via phone, face by face; Setting up commercial printers for business customers; Setting up small networks (LAN);

2016.09 - 2018.01

Company: EPS LT Company website: eps.lt

Position: Application Administrator

- Second level application support and analysis
- Identifying and correcting specific technical issues, incidents and problems related to IT applications and solutions
- Resolving and fixing complex incidents and problems
- Setting-up, configuring, supporting and maintaining applications based on IIS, $\ensuremath{\mathsf{MSSQL}}$ and .NET
- Preparing application-relevant documentation
- Generating custom XML and MSSQL based reports

2014.07 - 2016.09

Company: EPS LT Company website: eps.lt Position: Engineer

- 1. Monitoring. Company information systems monitoring (Nagios, Cacti, EPS E2E, EPS Domino);
- 2. Incident Management:
- a. Incident Recording (incident management system);
- b. Informing interested parties;
- c. Solving I level incidents;
- d. II + level of escalation of incidents;
- e. Incident Closure and documentation;
- 3. The company's computer workstation installation and maintenance;
- 4. Payment terminal Preparation for use;
- 5. Regular submission of proposals for existing processes and procedures to the immediate superior.

_ ---

Company: alterDomus

Company website: www.alterdomus.com/ Position: Application Support Engineer

Education

2019 - 2022

Educational institution: Abbey College Australia

Specialty: Telecommunications and Information Technology

Degree: Advanced vocational

2014 - 2016

Educational institution: Vilniaus Gediminas Technical University

Specialty: Electronics Engineering

Degree: Master

2009 - 2013

Educational institution: Vilniaus Gediminas Technical University Specialty: Electronic Equipment and Computer Hardware

Degree: Higher (bachelor)

Languages

Language	Speaking	Understanding	Writing
Russian	Perfect	Perfect	Good
Lithuanian	Good	Perfect	Good
English	Good	Perfect	Good
Polish	Average	Good	Good

Computer knowledge

Photoshop

Experienced up to 1 y.

PowerPoint

Experienced 3-4 y.

Word

Experienced 3-4 y.

Windows Server

Skillfull >3years

XML

Skillfull >2years

asterisk

Beginner

So far I'm starting to get my head around this technology. Being a student at Abbey College Australia I've got a project to build simple WebRTC solution

AWS cloud

Beginner
Azure Cloud Beginner
JavaScript Beginner my github https://github.com/AndzejK
Linux Beginner I've been exploring Ubuntu distribution. I've gone from Kernel to User space. I find Linux/Unix very fascinating OS; therefore, I'd like to dig deep into it.
MS Sql Beginner 1-2 y.
MySql Beginner basics
Python Beginner basics github.com/AndzejK
AutoCAD
up to 1 y.
C++ basics
Excel
1-2 y.
HTML
3-4 y.

Courses, seminars

2018.09

Mac OS X

>1 year

Duration (in hours): 240

Organiser: Greenwich English College

Title: Cambridge Certificate in Advanced English (CAE)

I have done this course two times since there was a high quality course and to my mind it was not enough to digest given information per one course.

Have certificate

2018.07

Duration (in hours): 240

Organiser: Greenwich English College

Title: Cambridge Certificate in Advanced English (CAE)

I was trained how to imply real-world English skills in speaking, writing, reading and listening, use and select the right grammar and structure to convey ideas fluently, accurately and naturally also I expanded my vocabulary

Have certificate

2018.03

Duration (in hours): 240

Organiser: Greenwich English College

Title: Cambridge First Certificate in English (FCE)

I have learned how to convey ideas fluently in English using correct grammar and sentence structure, a wider English vocabulary related to common topics and abstract themes. Finally I was toughth how to write longer, more complex pieces of writing such as essays, reports and reviews

Have certificate

2018.01

Duration (in hours): 100

Organiser: Greenwich English College

Title: English for business

I was tought to understand and use business specific language, learn everyday words and phrases suitable for working in an English speaking country, take part in debates and deliver professional business presentations in English and also apply effective negotiation skills.

Have certificate

2017.10

Duration (in hours): 20 Organiser: Barclays Title: UNIX Academy Have certificate

Other info

Driver licence: B

Hobbies: As hobbies I'm expanding knowledge in every aspect of my life. To begin with, reading books on neurology, human psychology and finishing off learning about an ethical hacking.